Delicious.
可口的。
Hey, SpongeBob.
嘿，海绵宝宝。
Hi, Sandy.
嗨，桑迪。
Nice of ya to drop in.
很高兴你能过来。
Check it out.
一探究竟。
I science'd up
a new invention.
我科学了
一项新发明。
I call it
the Anthropomorphizer.
我称之为
拟人化者。
- Ohh.
- Allow me to demonstrate.
- 哦。
- 请允许我演示一下。
Ahh! Ahh! Ooh.
啊！啊！哦。
- Wow!
- Yay!
- 哇！
- 耶！
both: Yoo-hoo!
两人：哟吼！
Seasoning!
调料！
- Ahh!
- Voila! Instant life.
- 啊！
- 瞧！ Instant life.
both: Ooh! Whoo-hoo!
两人：哦！呼呼！
Thank you. Thank you.
谢谢。谢谢。
Sandy, can it really bring
anything to life?
桑迪，它真的能带来吗？
有什么生活吗？
You can bet the farm on it.
你可以用农场做赌注。
Even a krabby patty?
甚至是蟹肉饼？
Yep. I reckon so.
是的。我认为是这样。
Order up!
赶快下单吧！
It lives!
My Krabby Patty lives!
它还活着！
我的蟹黄派还活着！
My, what odd sensations.
天啊，多么奇怪的感觉啊。
I feel like--
well, like I can feel!
我感觉就像——
好吧，就像我能感觉到的！
That's called livin'.
这就是所谓的活着。
You can walk and talk,
可以边走路边说话
and I reckon you got a few
thoughts up in the ol' bun too.
我想你有一些
老发髻里也有想法。
Hmm, I reckon I do!
嗯，我想我是的！
I can't believe it. A real
krabby patty who can talk,
我简直不敢相信。一个真实的
会说话的克拉比帕蒂，
and I can talk back to it,
and we can talk about
我可以反驳它，
我们可以谈谈
everything we love,
because I never knew
我们所爱的一切，
因为我从来不知道
what krabby patties loved,
but now I can know,
蟹肉饼喜欢什么，
但现在我可以知道，
and it can know what I know,
because I love krabby patties
它可以知道我所知道的，
因为我喜欢蟹肉饼
and I can show you what I love
in Bikini Bottom!
我可以告诉你我喜欢什么
在比基尼底部！
Well, double my cheese.
好吧，我的奶酪加倍。
I'm in.
我进来了
Yahoo!
雅虎！
Welp, I've created life
from nothing but fast food.
韦尔普，我创造了生命
除了快餐之外什么也没有。
I reckon I'm the smartest
squirrel in the world.
我认为我是最聪明的
世界上的松鼠。
Whoa!
哇！
Heh-heh?
呵呵？
Mm?
毫米？
Mm.
毫米。
Ooh! Ugh!
哦！啊!
This is Jellyfish Fields.
这里是水母田。
♪ La-la, la-la-la,
la-la-la, la-la-la, la-la ♪
♪ 啦啦啦啦啦啦，
啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦♪
It's where my friends and I
go jellyfishing.
这是我和我的朋友们的地方
去钓水母。
What the?
什么？
Especially new friends
like you.
尤其是新朋友
像你一样。
Ooh.
哦。
And look, Krabby Patty.
瞧，克拉比·帕蒂。
I even brought an extra little
net so you can learn how to--
我什至还额外带了一点
NET，这样你就可以学习如何——
Whoa!
哇！
Oh, you caught me! Ha-ha.
哦，你抓住了我！哈哈。
Ahh! Ahh!
啊！啊！
Ha-ha! Ahh!
哈哈！啊！
Ahhh!
啊啊！
Ew. Drop it.
呃。放下它。
You don't know
where that nasty patty's been.
你不知道
那个讨厌的小馅饼在哪里。
Hey. That nasty
Krabby Patty is my friend.
嘿。那个讨厌的
克拉比帕蒂是我的朋友。
Whoa!
哇！
Whoa-oh-oh! Oof!
哇哦哦！钱币！
both: Ahh! Yeow!
两人：啊！哟！
You need to be more careful,
Krabby Patty.
你需要更加小心，
克拉比·帕蒂。
You can't help it
that you're delicious.
你无能为力
你很好吃。
Oh-ho-ho-ho! Ay-ay-ay!
噢-嗬-嗬-嗬！哎哎哎！
This is Goofy Goober's,
这是高飞·古伯的，
the tastiest ice cream joint
in town.
最美味的冰淇淋店
在城里。
Everyone looks so happy.
每个人看起来都很高兴。
I want to be happy like them, SpongeBob.
我想像海绵宝宝一样快乐。
♪ Oh, I'm a Goofy Goober yeah,
you're a Goofy Goober, yeah ♪
♪ 哦，我是个傻瓜，是的，
你是个傻瓜，是的 ♪
Ooh.
哦。
Yoo-hoo.
哟吼。
Good sir.
好先生。
Your happiest
Gooberberry Sunrise for two.
你最幸福
古伯贝利日出两人份。
Sharing with ourselves
today, are we?
与我们自己分享
今天，我们是吗？
Huh? No, I'm sharing
with my new friend...
啊？不，我正在分享
和我的新朋友...
Krabby Patty!
蟹蟹帕蒂！
Ahh!
啊！
I'll save you.
我会救你的。
Whoa!
哇！
Ugh!
啊!
Come on, Krabby Patty,
we're leaving.
来吧，克拉比帕蒂，
我们要走了。
And I am never coming back
to a place
我再也不会回来
到一个地方
that would eat a customer.
那会吃掉顾客。
K, see you tomorrow.
K，明天见。
Oh, I'm sorry everyone keeps
trying to eat you, Krabby Patty.
哦，对不起大家都保留了
想吃掉你，蟹黄派蒂。
You must be having
the worst day of your life.
你一定有
你一生中最糟糕的一天。
I've gotta say,
我不得不说，
it hasn't been what I thought.
这不是我想的那样。
No matter how many times I jump
in someone's mouth,
不管我跳多少次
在某人的嘴里，
they still won't swallow me.
他们仍然不会吞掉我。
Wait, you were jumping
into their mouths on purpose?
等等，你跳起来了
故意放进他们嘴里吗？
Of course. Doesn't everyone
want to be eaten?
当然。不是每个人
想被吃掉吗？
No way.
At least I don't think so.
决不。
至少我不这么认为。
Well, I want to be eaten,
and I want to be eaten now!
嗯，我想被吃掉，
我现在就想被吃掉！
Wait, no. You can't.
等等，不。你不能。
Oh, yes I can.
哦，是的，我可以。
Krabby Patty, come back!
克拉比帕蒂，回来吧！
Huh?
啊？
Over here, kids.
在这里，孩子们。
I think you're ready
for solid foods.
我想你已经准备好了
用于固体食物。
kids: Ahh!
孩子们：啊！
I won't let them slobber on you.
我不会让他们向你流口水。
kids: Ugh! Oof! Whoa! Ugh!
孩子们：呃！钱币！哇！啊!
Move it, moppet.
移动它，毛孩。
Scram, squirt.
滚开，喷。
Ugh!
啊!
Ahh!
啊！
- Ugh!
- 呃！
My babies!
我的宝贝们！
Whoa!
哇！
Oh!
哦！
Ugh!
啊!
Patty, come back!
帕蒂，回来吧！
Well, if I can't get my hands
on a krabby patty,
好吧，如果我拿不到我的手
放在蟹肉饼上，
then at least I can go on
that ski trip I always wanted.
那么至少我可以继续
我一直想要的滑雪之旅。
Huh?
啊？
Never mind.
Skiing is for jerks.
没关系。
滑雪是混蛋的事。
Hey, krabby patty, Over here.
嘿，蟹肉饼，在这里。
I'd like to have a word with...
我想和...说句话
you?
你？
- Eat me! Eat me! Eat me!
- Ahh!
- 吃我吧！吃我吧！吃我吧！
- 啊！
I've gotta fit in here.
Come on.
我必须适应这里。
快点。
There you are.
你就在那里。
Sorry, Plankton.
对不起，浮游生物。
Krabby Patty here thinks
that he wants to--
克拉比帕蒂认为
他想要——
Go away.
离开。
I need to be alone.
我需要一个人呆着。
I don't get it, Krabby Patty.
我不明白，克拉比·帕蒂。
Don't you want to stay with me
and be my friend?
你不想和我在一起吗
做我的朋友吗？
Of course I do, SpongeBob.
我当然知道，海绵宝宝。
But jellyfishing and ice cream,
但是水母和冰淇淋，
well,
they're for people like you.
嗯，
它们适合像你这样的人。
I'm different.
我不一样。
It's like how your purpose
is making people happy
就像你的目的一样
使人们快乐
by feeding them,
通过喂养它们，
my purpose is making people
happy by feeding them me.
我的目的是让人们
我很高兴给他们喂食。
You know what, Krabby Patty?
你知道吗，克拉比帕蒂？
I get it now.
我现在明白了。
And I'm going to help you be
the best meal you can be.
我会帮助你
你能吃到的最好的一餐。
Let's find the perfect mouth
to gobble you up.
让我们找到完美的嘴巴
吞噬你。
Oh, I'm one happy patty!
哦，我是一只快乐的小馅饼！
Auditions are now open
to eat my friend Patty.
试镜现已开放
吃我的朋友帕蒂。
Next, please.
接下来请。
Only I know how to truly savor
a krabby patty.
只有我知道如何真正品味
蟹肉饼
Therefore,
I believe I should have
因此，
我相信我应该有
the distinction of eating you.
吃掉你的区别。
Hmm.
唔。
Ahh.
啊。
Ooh! Ahh! Ohh! Ugh! Ew!
哦！啊！哦！啊!呃！
I think you savored that
last one a little too long.
我想你很喜欢这个
最后一张有点太长了。
Next.
下一个。
Hmph! Well, I never...
哼！嗯，我从来没有...
Heh-heh-heh-heh, heh.
嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿。
Ohh, what a delicious-looking
little man.
哦，多么美味的样子
小男人。
I could chew on you for hours.
我可以咀嚼你几个小时。
Yeah, I think your mouth
is already occupied, mister.
是的，我认为你的嘴
已经有人了，先生。
Ohh.
哦。
both: Next!
两人：下一个！
Ahh!
both: Next!
啊！
两人：下一个！
Next.
下一个。
Hmm?
唔？
Howdy--ohh.
你好——哦。
Why the long faces?
为什么脸这么长？
Aw pickle chips.
噢泡菜片。
All I want is to be eaten.
我想要的只是被吃掉。
Ohh.
哦。
But we just can't find
the perfect mouth.
但我们就是找不到
完美的嘴。
Well... oh!
嗯……哦！
Maybe SpongeBob could give you
the ol' bite and chew.
也许海绵宝宝可以给你
咬和咀嚼。
Mm.
毫米。
Mm-mm-mm.
嗯嗯嗯。
Ahh.
啊。
Great teeth,
好大的牙齿，
healthy tongue...
健康的舌头...
Minty-fresh breath.
薄荷清新口气。
Spread my ketchup,
the perfect mouth.
涂上我的番茄酱，
完美的嘴。
It would be an honor, SpongeBob.
这将是一种荣幸，海绵宝宝。
Oh, no, Krabby Patty.
哦，不，克拉比·帕蒂。
The honor is mine.
荣誉是我的。
Bon appétit, friend.
祝你胃口好，朋友。
Ahh...
啊...
Halt!
停止！
I deserve this patty.
我值得这个肉饼。
I'm clearly the hungriest.
我显然是最饿的。
Wah!
哇！
both: Whoa!
两人：哇！
All this for little old me.
这一切都是为了小老我。
Ha-ha. Why if you'd told me
when I was a lifeless pile
哈哈。为什么如果你告诉我
of ingredients
that someday I'd...
成分的
有一天我会...
Huh?
啊？
Welp,
I guess it got what it wanted.
韦尔普，
我想它得到了它想要的。
So, Gary, how was it?
那么，加里，怎么样？
- Wow.
- Halt!
- 哇。
- 停下来！
I blame the squirrel
for this fracas.
我责怪松鼠
为了这场争吵。
She made us turn on each other
with her wicked,
她让我们互相攻击
与她的恶人，
wicked science.
邪恶的科学。
Well, science giveth,
嗯，科学给出，
and science taketh away.
科学带走了。
Take me away, science.
带我走吧，科学。
Yee-haw!
呀呀！